# jhon anderson puentes hernandez



apxanderson02@gmail.com



3052433991



linkedin.com/in/jhon-anderson-puenteshernandez-32118420b



https://jhon2410.github.io/portafolio/

## **Summary**

Experience applying the MERN development stack, sufficient knowledge in different programming languages such as Java, Python, PHP, JavaScript. I am familiar with the most famous layout patterns like MVC. agile methodologies such as SCRUM, XP. 2 years of experience working on own projects and small commissions. Intermediate level of English.

spa management, reactive pages and communication to endpoints of the rest api, and relational and nonrelational databases.

GITHUB: https://github.com/Jhon2410

Technologies I have used:

- > Javascript
- > Typewritten text
- > React
- > Vue
- > Angular
- > Node js
- > Java
- > PHP
- > Laravel
- > Django
- > Flask
- > Express
- > Boostrap 5
- > Sass less
- > tailwind
- > quasar
- > Ajax (axios, search, jquery)
- > GraphQI
- > Jsonwebtokens
- > MongoDB
- > MySql
- > Postgresql
- > Hit
- > HTML5
- > CSS3
- > Git and GitHub
- > Heroku

# **Experience**



## Full-stack Developer

Profesional independiente

Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

# Frontend Web Developer

Mar 2020 - Present (1 year 11 months +)

#### **Education**

### **Universidad Surcolombiana**

Ingeniería, Ingeniería de software Aug 2019 - Jun 2024

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

METODOLOGIA DE LA PROGRAMACION DE SISTEMAS INFORMATICOS -

Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA) 9210002460334CC1004343925C

\* APLICACION DE LA CALIDAD DEL SOFTWARE EN EL PROCESO DE

**DESARROLLO** - Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA) 9123002460258CC1004343925C

DESARROLLO WEB CON PHP - Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA) 9123002459879CC1004343925E

## **Skills**

Ingeniería • Resolución de problemas • Software Development • Web Development • Design Patterns • Investigación • Estrategia • React.js • Node.js • MongoDB